myprivatetutor.com 2017-03-14

# My Private Tutor.com - Privacy Policy

## Application and Scope

Stated below is the Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy") of Myprivatetutor.com ("Website," "Site", "we", "our" or "us").

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to identify the personal information we may collect, describe how you can review and make changes to that personal information, describe how you can learn about changes to the Privacy Policy, and provide you with a mechanism to opt-out of certain marketing activities.

Please take a moment to review the terms of this Privacy Policy. Your access and use of our Website is conditioned upon your acceptance of the terms stated herein. If you do not agree with one or more of the terms stated in this Privacy Policy, then your only remedy is to refrain from using our Website.  From time to time, this Privacy Policy may change.  Where a change is made to this policy we will inform users accordingly. This may be by way of a public message posted on the site, or by a message which we send to you personally. In addition, you are advised to periodically check this policy (and the Terms of Use) for changes.

You are also required to review and agree to our [Terms of Use](https://www.myprivatetutor.com/terms), which govern your use of this Website.

Please note that we reserve the right to modify, limit, add or delete, without notice, any of the services discussed in this Privacy Policy.

## Information We Collect From You

We automatically collect information about your internet connection, including but not limited to:

  * The name of the Internet domain you used to access the Internet 
  * The IP address of the web site from which you linked directly to our Site
  * The content you submit
  * The date and time you accessed our Site
  * The pages you visited

This information ("Non-Personal Information") does not identify you personally. We use this Non-Personal Information to monitor the effectiveness of the Site and Products, to identify areas of interest and to consider potential improvements to the Site, apps and products.

We request that you provide certain personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") when you register to participate in services of our Website. We request that you provide name, mailing address, telephone numbers, e-mail address, date of birth, qualification certificate, Aadhar Card, PAN Card, and payment information such as credit card, PayPal and other financial information as applicable. We also require you to submit a user name and password of your choice for future access to your information. Your user name and password is to remain confidential and you should not share this information with anyone. We request you to provide us information regarding your personal accounts and/or profiles on third-party social networking sites such as Facebook and Twitter so that we can use it to advertise our services by stating that you use services of our Website. Providing such information is voluntary, and by providing such information, you consent to our collection and use of it, as described in this Privacy Policy. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from a child under the age of eighteen (18) without prior guardian consent. Our Website and products contain features useful to children; therefore, children should not be granted access to any passwords or use of the parent or guardian’s account without direct monitoring and supervision by the parent or guardian. We are not responsible for any unauthorized use of accounts, and we encourage everyone to protect their passwords and not disclose them to anyone. You may choose not to provide Personal Information via the Website, and you may choose not to participate in the Website.

We collect information when you send us an inquiry, suggestion, comment or request including any email or mailing address or telephone number you provide so that we may respond. We collect information when you choose to participate in a survey or promotion.

## Use of Your Personal Information

We use Personal Information obtained from you to process our services. In the process, you must provide additional financial information such as credit card number, expiration date, wire transfer or account information. This information is used for billing purposes and to fulfill services.

We do not disclose any Personal Information to non-affiliated third parties, except as necessary for us to provide our services to you, or as permitted by law, (like giving you credit for rewards, carrying out a transaction you have requested, operating or managing our business, or responding to legal process).

We may disclose any Personal Information we collect with our affiliates, including for purposes of internal audit, management, billing or administrative purposes including defending and bringing legal actions.

We are concerned about identity theft and the practice currently known as "phishing". Our top priority is to protect you from identity theft. We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, your account ID, login password, or national identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication.

## Sharing Your Information

We use a credit card processing company to bill users for purchases and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. We use third party service providers, contractors and clients to facilitate the Website and the services we provide, and they may have access to Personal Information. In the event we merge or consolidate with another institution, Personal Information may be transferred to the successor entity. We may also disclose Personal Information if we are required to do so by law.

We may share Non-Personal Information, including aggregated demographic and statistical information, with our affiliates, partners, contractors, clients and others. Such information could be used to provide us with statistical or other analysis.

We may share Non-Personal Information with our affiliates, partners, contractors, clients and others in connection with reviews or surveys that you submit to us to post on our Website or other websites or on third-party social networking sites such as Facebook and Twitter.

## Feedback

We collect feedback from users about their experience with other users of the Service. Feedback that you provide on our Website will be publicly viewable.

## Email Policy

We may send you emails for

  * Customer service required to maintain our Website program and services; and 
  * Promotion of our Services;

If you do not want to receive our newsletters, offers and service information, simply contact us [contact@myprivatetutor.com](mailto:contact@myprivatetutor.com) and be sure to include the e-mail address where such information is being sent, and state that you no longer want to receive MyPrivateTutor.com information and updates. 

## Refer a Friend Policy

You may opt to use our Refer a Friend service to refer your friends to become members of our Website. We will automatically send an email inviting your friend to visit our Website and products and become members of our Website. Your friend may request us to move their information by contacting us at [contact@myprivatetutor.com](mailto:contact@myprivatetutor.com).

## Use of Cookies

The use of cookies enables us to enhance your visits to the Website. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that are transferred to your computer's hard drive through your web browser. The help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, but this may limit your ability to use some features of the Website. Cookies enable us to recognize your browser and provide features that are tailored to your needs.

We may use information from cookies for purposes of planning and tracking, as well as assessing the technical function of the Website and products. We may also use cookies to track information about which pages you visit within the Website to help us gauge the effectiveness of the Website or our services or products.

## International Use

If you are located outside India and choose to provide information to us, we transfer and process your Personal Information to India or in other locations that we decide necessary or convenient in order to provide you with efficient and effective service. By accepting this Privacy Policy you agree to such transfer of your Personal Information to India. Your information may be transferred to and maintained on computers located outside of your country, state, province, or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction.

## Linked Sites

We may provide links on the Website to other sites of interest or to sites that perform services for us. We do not review or endorse the content of these sites or guarantee that they will abide by this Privacy Policy. Your use of such linked sites is subject to the terms and conditions and privacy policies of the providers of those sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Website and to read the privacy statements of each Website that collects Personal Information.

## Security Measures

While we strive to secure your Personal Information, even reasonable security measures do not guarantee the security of any information you transmit via the internet, including information submitted to our Website. We cannot guarantee that information it seeks to protect will be protected under all circumstances, including those beyond its reasonable control. By accessing our Website, you agree that you transmit information to our Website via our Website at your own risk.

## Children

We do not knowingly collect any information from children under the age of eighteen (18). Any person who provides Personal information to us represents that they are 18 years of age or older. Any person under the age of 18 shall be represented by their guardian. If we learn that Personal information is collected from user under 18 years of age without proper representation by guardian then we will take appropriate steps to delete such information.

## Reviewing Information

You may review your information at any time by logging into the Website. You may make changes to the information you have submitted at any time through the Website. You may contact us if you wish to discuss any issues regarding your information.

## Legal requests and business transfers

MyPrivateTutor may disclose personal information when we believe such action is necessary to comply with the law or enforce or apply our Terms of Service. In the event of a change in control of MyPrivateTutor’s business, personal information may be exchanged as part of a merger, sale, or other business transfer. If such a transfer makes a material change to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you of any changes.

## Advertising

Advertisements appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non-personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

## Google Adsense

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at [www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

## Changes to This Policy

We reserve the right to change, modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time without notice. When we change, modify and/or amend this Privacy Policy, the revised Privacy Policy will be posted on our Website. Any revised Privacy Policy will only apply prospectively to information collected or modified after the effective date of the revised policy. You are responsible for periodically reviewing the latest Privacy Policy as posted on our Website. Your continued use of our Website manifests your assent to any changes made to this Privacy Policy and/or the corresponding Terms of Use.

## Your choices

Please remember to help keep the Site secure by never sharing your username or password. If you think your password may have been compromised, please change it immediately or contact MyPrivateTutor for additional assistance. MyPrivateTutor may send you email communications periodically detailing new features or promotions on the Site. You may unsubscribe from these messages by using the link at the bottom of the email. We may also send you email messages about the status of your account or any notices as required by law. You may not opt-out of receiving these administrative emails so long as you continue to use this voluntary service. If you wish to terminate your account, please contact us.

## Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site,   
**Please contact us at:**

#### MyPrivateTutor.com

####  C/o: Brishti Technologies Pvt Ltd

1209, Purbachal Main Road  
Prince Anwar Shah Connector  
Near Bypass Abhishikta Spencers  
Kolkata -700078  
West Bengal, India  
+91 33 2484 4706
